flashpoint1985.com 2016-05-13

# Privacy Policy | Bohemia Interactive

Updated: 11.11.2015 

###  Your Privacy 

Privacy is an issue that We know is important to you and therefore it is very important to Us as well. Any information We collect about You will be used for the sole purpose of helping Us to serve you better. 

In this document, “Company", “We”, “Us” means BOHEMIA INTERACTIVE a.s. residing at Stříbrná Lhota 747, 252 10 Mníšek pod Brdy, Czech Republic, registered in the Commercial Register kept by the Municipal Court in Prague, section B, insert 9791 (Id.No.: 272 18 864, DIČ: CZ 272 18 864) and its affiliates and subsidiaries.  
"User", “You” means the person, company or institution that uses the Services.  
“Services” are services, games and websites operated by the Company and used by the User. 

This Privacy policy is a part the terms of use of any of our Services and so when you agree to the respective terms of each of the Services, you are also agreeing with this Privacy policy. 

You may be sure that We will never disclose this personal information to a third party without your consent. You agree that We are allowed to share your personal information with the Company's affiliates for the purpose of operating the Services. 

All personal data is protected from disclosure to and use by third parties, and used only for the purpose of operating Services of the Company and its Affiliates, and communication with the User as governed by the laws of the Czech Republic, in the sense of Law No. 101/2000 Coll., on the [Protection of Personal Data](https://www.uoou.cz/en/vismo/zobraz_dok.asp?id_org=200156&id_ktg=1107), as amended. 

You have the right to access and review your personal data, We hold about you and also to ask Us for explanation of which, why and how We store your data. If the personal data in our system is wrong, insufficient or irrelevant, then you have the right to make sure that it is corrected or removed. In order to exercise these rights or to ask any questions related to this policy, please send Us an e-mail at [support@bistudio.com](mailto:support@bistudio.com) . 

###  Non-personal Data 

Our Services may use tools or third party analytical software to automatically collect and use certain non-personal data (data which cannot be used to directly identify you). We use this data to analyze general user behavior in our services and to help Us improve our Services. 

###  Children 

We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If you are a parent or a legal guardian of a child under 13, then you may request to review the personal information of your child, to have this information deleted, or to revoke permission for further collection or use of your child’s personal information by contacting Us at [support@bistudio.com](mailto:support@bistudio.com). 

###  Updates 

As the world of laws and games may change quickly, We reserve the right to add to or change this policy from time to time. When We do so, We will revise the "effective" date at the top of the policy.

Your continued use of Services will signify your acceptance of the changes to this Privacy Policy. 

###  Cookies 

In order to improve your experience on our Site and in our Services We use cookies to remember who you are. More information about how and why We use cookies may be found [here](https://www.bistudio.com/cookie-policy).
